放假啦  小婊子们
School's out, bitches.
恭喜  格林德尔的学生们
Congratulations, Greendale students!
我们又挺过了一年时光  依然屹立不倒
We've pulled off another year and we're still standing.
甩你一脸  卫生检查员
Take that, health inspector,
建筑检查员  基金会监察员
building inspector, foundation inspector,
水管检查员  地质学家
water line inspector, geologist,
灭虫员  水管工  还有老爹
exterminator, plumber, and dad.
阿布蒂
Abed.
你拿个节拍器是要作甚
Why bring a metronome?
我觉得这个声音可以着重强调出
I thought the sound might accentuate
我们最后一次会议最后几秒钟的急切感
the anxious idleness of our last meeting's final seconds.
干得漂亮  点子烂透
Good job, bad idea.
好了  完成了
Okay, that is done.
-耶  -还有个事
- Yay! - There's more!
这事老激动人心了
This one is exciting.
我们得给「拯救格林德尔委员会」重新取名了
We have to rename the Save Greendale committee,
因为格林德尔已经被拯救成功了
due to the fact that Greendale is done being saved!
你觉得这事比暑假还兴奋吗
You think that's more exciting than summer?
咋的  耽误你晒太阳了  哥们
Oh, am I stealing your rays, dude?
拜托  多棒啊
Come on, it's neat!
我们的任务终于完成了  彻底完成
Our mission is finally accomplished, once and for all,
那我们现在要叫什么名字
so what do we call ourselves now?
完成者
The accomplishers.
过气人
The obsoletists.
史蒂芬·金的捕梦网
Steven King's dreamcatchers.
苏珊
Susan.
你们是在给自己找不痛快
You guys are rebelling against yourselves.
你们明白的吧
You get that, right?
当下品牌的趋势是要与众不同
The current trend in branding is unique,
简单易懂  发音易记的胡说八道
simplistic, phonetically memorable gibberish.
奶头长勺怎么样
How about nipple dippers?
我喜欢奶头长勺
I like nipple dippers.
-好  -大伙呀
- Yes. - You guys.
-好  -这个网址尚未被占用
- OK. - Ooh, nippledippers.com is available.
赶紧抢
Grab that mother.
-搞定  -奶头长勺们  听好了
- Done. - Nipple dippers, listen up.
院长来短信
Text from the dean.
先别走  我快到了
Don't leave yet, I'm almost there.
特殊庆祝
Special celebration.
成功过完了一个没玩COS的学期
Just finished entire semester without wearing a single silly outfit.
我都没注意  真不错
I didn't even notice. Good for him.
大家安安
Hey everybody!
我成功了
I made it!
事实上铃声刚响过的时候
Obviously, I binged pretty hard there
我可是苦苦往身上套啊  不过
after the bell rang but,
我成功了
I made it!
你们是要出去庆个祝啥的吗
Are you guys going out to celebrate or something?
能带我一个不
Maybe I'll tag along,
这一年我也累坏了  喝点酒解解乏
it's been a tough year, I could use a drink.
我们要去布雷塔的酒吧  只等着
We were gonna to Britta's bar whenever- Oh.
老妈发话结束这一年的工作了
Mother time is willing to call it a year.
那行吧  我们收工了  暑假快乐
Kay fine, we're done, happy summer.
奶头长勺们喝酒免费
Nipple dippers drink for free!
酒钱我自己掏  这名头我可称不起
I'll pay for my drinks, I'm not acknowledging that title.
某人欠我注册域名的十块钱
Someone owes me ten bucks for the domain.
我就去不了了
I won't be able to join you.
我要踏上前往加州的路途
I gotta get on the road to California.
我通过领英网找了个工作
I got a job through LinkedIn.
啥  不可思议
What? That's crazy!
居然真有人用领英网
People use LinkedIn?
没有  领英网雇我去查查
No, LinkedIn hired me to help figure out
为什么大家不用这个网
why people don't use it.
而且我的一个高中女同学
Also, I have an old lady friend I went to high school with who
上周刚刚恢复单身
just became un-married last week
我想去瞅瞅她
and I thought I'd look her up.
您老速度够快的
Wow, you work fast.
应该说是够慢的
Or actually, very slow.
不管怎样  祝你好运
Either way, good luck.
你还会回来吗  埃尔罗伊
Are you coming back Elroy?
差不多吧
I think so.
可能
Probably,
大概
maybe.
暑假愉快
Have a great summer.
■
本字幕首发于字幕组网站
www.ZiMuZu.tv 欢迎交流
翻  译    别扭大菜
翻  译    DayDay·槑·郗涵
翻  译    废柴章鱼X
翻  译    夕橙
时 间 轴    姜姜
后  期    鱼骨头
顾  问    Greydale
校对/总监    夕橙
本季结束  感谢有你  有缘再见
废柴联盟
第六季  第十三集[季终]
你们觉得酒吧戏总会从捣台球开始吗
You guys think bars scene always have to start at a billiards shot?
还是说每次镜头一开始是捣台球的话
Or do you think every time someone takes a shot a in billiards
就不知不觉地拍上了酒吧戏了
they start a new bar scene without knowing it?
什么
What?
你就说一句就好  闭嘴阿布蒂
You can just say shut up Abed.
好了  问我还会不会回来
Okay, ask me if I'm coming back?
你还会回来吗
Are you coming back?
会啊
Yeah.
可能
Probably.
大概
Maybe.
那算个什么啊  你们说
I mean what was that, right?
那算爱尔兰式道别
That was an Irish goodbye.
我们给他来个爱尔兰式守夜[悼念]
Let's give it an Irish wake.
六年了  同志们
Six years guys.
奶头长勺们
Nipple dippers.
安妮去哪了
Where's Annie?
我说实话你们别介意
I mean no offense to you guys
她可是唯一懂我的人
but she's the only one that gets me.
她说她去参加面试了
She said she had an interview?
六年了
Six years.
是六季了吧  阿布蒂
Six seasons, right Abed?
别跟他提这茬
Don't put a nickel in him.
别歇着了各位
Stop mitigating everyone.
-阿布蒂  第七季会怎样  -要命了
- So Abed, what happens in Season Seven? - Oh, man.
我不知道第七季会是什么样
I don't know how likely season seven is.
哪个剧还会在六季之后创出新高峰啊
I mean, what show ever peaks after season six?
辛普森一家  宋飞正传  南方公园  老友记
Simpsons, Seinfeld, South Park, Friends.
那些剧没有每年演员都大换血
Those shows weren't hemorrhaging characters every year.
我不喜欢那个词  大换血
Oh, I don't like that word, hemorrhaging.
我来想办法看要怎么处理
I'll see what I can do.
如果雪瑞回来了  会改变你的意向吗
What if Shirley came back, would that change your disposition?
雪瑞会让我们回归公式化
Shirley could get us back on formula,
但我觉得依然无法挽回大局
but I don't see it turning us around.
抱歉  我们什么公式
Sorry, what's our formula?
基本上就是
Well, basically.
我的设定是太过自命不凡
I have a placeholder so set up it,
导致一旦效仿就变得很像笑点
makes analogies look like punchlines.
我的设定是没自知自明
My setup lacks awareness,
但我的笑点是啥不知道
but my punchline doesn't know.
滥用愤世嫉俗的笑话鄙视你刚刚说过的一切
Abusively cynical one liner dismissing everything you just said.
荒诞的反应
Absurd reaction.
大伙啊  我们能不能先把副线剧情放一放
You guys, can we put a pin in the B story
专注一下主线剧情好不好
and focus on the A story?
我不相信主线剧情  从始至终就是不信
I don't trust A stories. Never have, never will.
我曾经的形象设定是那么不可替代
I had a set up about a story that was so placeholder,
我的笑点在那五个字出现之前就有了
the punchline came five words early.
我也能打上标签好吗
And I can tag it too.
我要占用一小段时间来解释一下
I'll just take a moment to explain the risks involved
从现在到永远做出的决定所带来的所有风险
in all decisions made from here until eternity.
您是哪位啊
Who the hell are you?
我是弗兰·达特
I'm Frankie Dart.
咱这组合走得下去吗
Is this combination gonna work?
轮不到我来说
Not my place to say.
阿布蒂
Abed?
蜥蜴
Lizard.
消防栓
Fire hydrant.
奥巴马
Obama.
原野奇侠
Shane!
我对服饰挑选可是相当精心费时的
You know, I put time into what I do wardrobe wise.
其实有雪瑞没雪瑞  无所谓的
Yeah see, Shirley, no Shirley, what does it matter, right?
阿布蒂  我们不是公式
Abed, we're not formulas,
如果我真没有自知自明  我应该知道的
and if I had no self-awareness, I think I'd know.
万事万物都有特定的属性  懂吗
Things have a certain structure to them, you know?
如果偏离属性  我们会很奇怪
If we stray from it, we're weird,
如果太拘泥于属性  那也无聊
if we stick to it, we're boring.
可这更多只是你的脑洞而已吧  阿布蒂
Yeah, but isn't that more about the shape of your brain, Abed?
我说这话你可别介意啊
I mean, no offense or anything.
不过你的脑洞确实有点操蛋不是吗
But isn't the shape of your brain kinda fucked up?
你对第七季是怎么个设定
What's your season seven pitch?
我对你们在格林德尔的秋季学期的设定是
My pitch for your fall semester at Greendale
大家友好又开心  快乐同成长
is that everyone is nice and has fun and grows together.
雪瑞还是埃尔罗伊
Shirley or Elroy?
你看  你种族歧视了吧  哥们
See, that's racist, man.
雪瑞还是埃尔罗伊
Shirley or Elroy?
这叫种族歧视
That's racist.
他们俩都回归怎么样
How about they both come back?
要是再添上第三个黑人怎么样
How about there's a whole third black person?
他们都要坐哪
Where do they all sit?
爱坐哪坐哪呗  就像上世纪六十年代那样
They well they sit wherever they want to sit, as of the 1960s.
他们就坐在
They sit.
他们坐在
开脑洞设定就好
Just pitch it.
-别开脑洞  -我就要开脑洞
- Don't pitch it. - I'm pitching it.
你们知道吗
Guess what?
我做了一个东西
I made something.
我用布料做了一条腰带
I made a belt with fabric.
很可爱有没有
How cute is that?
我觉得很可爱  所以...
Well, I think that's very cute, so oh,
我爱你们大家
and I love you guys.
我有...我很愤怒
I've got, I'm angry
你们就应该投票  或者不投票
and you should vote or don't vote.
好耶  哈利路亚
Sweet! Hallelujah!
这样的时光太美好啦亲们
These are good times, baby.
美好时光啊妹子  美好的时光
Good times girl, good times.
我想起来了
Hey, I thought of something.
我们应该去那个
You know, we should go to the
去那个...去那个...去市场
to the to the, to to the market.
对呀
Yeah, we should.
那就跟我们之前的那个一样了不是吗
Well, wouldn't that be like a thing we saw,
我们不是已经做过了吗
and didn't we do that?
我们应该心存羞愧  应该变聪明些啊
So shouldn't we be more ashamed and clever?
应该让一切变得更加困难不是吗
And make everything more difficult?
没错  我觉得我们应该深深地感到悲哀
Yes, and I think we should be deeply sad.
我脑子有病
And I'm nuts.
但是我很快乐
But I'm happy.
我也很快乐
And I'm happy too.
而且  你们懂的  哈利路亚
And you know, hallelujah,
教堂  颂歌  街头文化
and church, and singing, and street wisdom.
你够了
Stop!
神经病  种族歧视  烂透了
Crazy, and racist, and terrible!
我同意  你这个脑洞开得太直线性了
I agree. You're being way too linear about this.
雪瑞  埃尔罗伊
Shirley, Elroy,
特洛伊  汉基是过去几季的人
Troy, Hickey, living in the past.
第七季不需要过去
Season seven don't need no past.
那你的脑洞设定是什么
What are you pitching?
不许脑洞
Don't pitch!
这是我开的脑洞
This is my pitch.
好啦  以上就是文件里
All right, that includes all notes and business
所有的事项
as it pertains to the files.
大家感觉如何
How are you guys doing?
妞  你感觉咋样
Babe, how you doing, girl?
我很好  什么都很好
I'm cool, it's all good.
安妮  你看起来好极了
Annie, you're looking fine.
谢谢
Thank you.
那我咧
Hey, what about me?
大家好  看看我
Hey everybody, look at me!
我是冰块头
I'm Ice Cube Head!
我的头是一块冰块儿
I've got an ice cube for a head.
我还能吃手机  所以你们放在我身边的手机
I also eat cell phones, so you better be careful
都得小心着点儿
with those cellphones around me,
因为在我老家手机的味道就像上等牛排
because they taste like prime rib where I'm from.
哈哈好家伙
Oh ho ho, boy.
想想我们以后要在一起的时间
Imagine the times we'll all get in together,
尤其是我用超能力解决你们所有问题的时候
especially when I use my powers to help solve all your problems.
这里的画面真是太火爆啦
it's getting crazy in here!
好了  我要回家了
All right, I'm going home.
什么
What?
亲们  我们刚刚结束了第六年
Guys, we just finished year six,
很辛苦的一年
and it was hard work.
我不想再为格林德尔操心了
And I don't wanna care about Greendale.
我不想将我短暂的人生浪费在
And I don't wanna spend my brief moment of humanity
即兴重复的概念片段上
doing conceptual riffs,
创作关于我们生活的虚拟电视剧
developing the imaginary TV show of our lives.
另外  你演得烂死了
By the way, terrible improv.
冰块头  什么鬼
Ice Cube Head?
你就是盯着饮料里的冰块想出来的吧
You were just looking at your drink.
被发现了
Busted.
安妮
Annie?
我通过面试了
I got the internship.
我得到实习职位  我要去FBI做实习生啦
I got the internship! I'm gonna intern for the FBI.
我这周就要走
I'll leave in a week.
整个暑假我都要在华盛顿了
I'll be in DC all summer.
小鸟终于要离巢了
You're leaving the nest.
那我可以用你的卧室咩
Can I have your bedroom?
如果你不回来  如果你不回来的话
If you don't come back, if you don't come back.
我肯定要回来的  可能吧
Well, I'm definitely coming back, probably.
也许  大概  说不定
Maybe, maybe, maybe.
好的  下一个议程
Okay, next order of business.
翁格先生  加瑞特又牵伦纳德的手了
Mr. Winger, Garrett's holding Leonard's hand again.
加瑞特  不许这样
Garrett, stop doing that.
我在号脉嘛
I'm checking for a pulse.
放开伦纳德
Hey, hands off the Leonard dice.
提问  下一次彩弹大战是什么时候
Question, when can we start the next paintball game?
我觉得这事强求不来
I don't think he can force it.
很多事情都是可以强求的
Lots of things can be forced,
比如人的脑袋可以穿过15厘米的水管什么的
like a human head through a six-inch drain pipe.
-什么  -骗你的啦
- What?  - Just kidding, pal.
请问格林德尔委员会现在在场的各位
Okay, did anyone on the sustained Greendale committee
谁把本周的作业做完了
do any of their assignments this week.
撕瓜奇
Scrunch.
不好意思哥儿们
Sorry, bro.
我不是给你打工的
I don't work for you.
是你给我打工
You work for me.
我是高科技土豪
I'm the tech billionaire
我买了你们这部烂戏  还削减你们的预算
that bought this dump and cuts your paycheck.
如果那点钱也算预算的话
If you can call that a paycheck.
我在珍珠港那会儿见过好多零呢
I've seen more zeroes over Pearl Harbor.
当年好几百个零呢[日本海军的零式战斗机]
There were hundreds of them.
烟雾弹把天都熏黑了
The sky was black with smoke bombs.
翁格  确认一下
Double click this, Winger.
该去工作的人是你
It's your job to work.
我们的工作是去派对
It is our job to party.
还有搞些轻率计划
And hatch harebrained schemes.
还有滚床单
And get laid.
还有最终把你们都留在这里
And eventually leave you here as well.
杰夫  你还好吗
Jeff, you okay?
我刚才太吃惊了
Oh, I, I was taken aback.
真是个大新闻
It's big news.
你们刚才都在干嘛
What have you guys been doing?
我们刚才...
We were just
在想怎么玩转第七季
looking for ways to make Season Seven work.
我们已经走过了六季了
I mean we've got through six seasons.
怎么个情况啊
I mean what's up with that?
第七季在哪儿啊
Where's season seven?
我们得好好想想第七季啊
I mean we gotta figure out season seven.
或者我们就出去逛逛算了
Or maybe we could just hang out.
对不起我来晚了
Sorry I'm late.
昨晚玩得太疯了
Last night was so insane,
疯得连「疯狂小丑团」都像正常小丑团了
it made the Insane Clown Posse look like the Well-adjusted Clown Posse.
能逃出你自己的真实年龄真是不容易啊
It must be hard work running away from your own age.
有谁见到我的电子烟了吗
Has anyone seen my e-cigarette?
应该为你们这种人办个慈善项目的
There should be a charity for people like you.
谢谢
Thank you.
从这里到FBI总部上班
I don't know if I can keep making the commute
我都不知道自己还做不做得下去
from here to the FBI headquarters.
布雷塔  阿布蒂  我得搬回来了
Britta, Abed, I'll have to move back in.
我已经搬去和他们住了
I moved in with them.
昌  FBI有你的档案哦
Chang, we have files.
马上搬走
Moving out.
安妮你压力太大了
You seem stressed, Annie.
FBI的实习是不是你在格林德尔
Are those last few criminology credits
很难拿的最后几个学分
you need hard to get at Greendale?
得了吧  格林德尔唯一难拿的
Please. The only credit that it's hard to get
是银行的信用吧[多义词]
at Greendale is from a bank.
只是  他们在匡蒂科也有这种学校
It's just, they have schools for this kind of stuff at Quantico.
跟你们在一起是很棒啦
Being with you guys is great,
但为什么对我来说是一个好机会呢
but why is this a good choice for me?
为什么观众不会为我惋惜呢
Why doesn't the audience feel sorry for me?
布雷塔  你爹妈被杀了
Britta, your parents have been murdered.
谁干的
By whom?
警方不插手此事
The police won't touch it.
他们说是双双殉情
They're calling it a double suicide.
布雷塔  放着我来
Britta, I got this.
你的脑洞版本要把安妮的回归建立在
You're proposing a version of the show in which Annie comes back,
我父母被杀的基础上
and it hinges on the murder of my parents.
就是个暂时设定嘛
It's a placeholder.
我只是说格林德尔永远需要法律课
I'm just saying there's always gonna be a need for law at Greendale.
大家还记得那个投菊大盗吗
You remember the ass Crack Bandit?
我记得吗  我说
Do I remember? I mean.
大家不都记得吗
Doesn't everybody.
谁都可能是那个强盗啊
Could have been anybody.
为什么我非得穿个纸尿裤
What is with this diaper thing?
是故意为了让我难堪吗
Is it about shaming me?
你还真想让一群人来为你穿戴啊
Do you really want a bunch of people dressing you?
试试无妨嘛
It would be polite to try.
杰夫  你能对这种事有兴趣是很好啦
It's nice to see you interested in this stuff, Jeff,
但第七季我会弃剧的
but I wouldn't watch that season.
我也是  你是不是想要个完美的第七季
Me, neither. You wanna know a perfect season seven?
我告诉你  参议员
Well, guess what Senator?
我们之前忍你骂我们恐怖分子
You were allowed to call us terrorists
是因为我们还没搬到国际水域上
before we moved to international waters,
但现在我们早已独立建国
but we're a nation now.
你丫再这么说就是宣战了
So I guess this is fucking war.
安妮  我需要你单刀出使华盛顿
Annie, I'm gonna need you to go to Washington.
-我好怕怕  -你还不够怕
- I'm scared. - Be more scared than that.
布雷塔
Britta.
抗议人群都慌成一团了
The protesters are scared.
他们要求你出面讲话
They need you to talk to them.
他们应该惊慌
They should be scared,
但他们不应该指望别人领导指挥他们
but they shouldn't need a leader to tell them what to do.
我们生为自由身  却要面对满世界的谎言
We're all born free into a world of lies.
不过我们还是先说说你吧
But let's talk about you for a second, though.
我不再是笑柄了
Well, I'm not a joke anymore.
我已彻底变性
I'm strictly transgender.
彻底告别以往的糟乱玩意儿了
I'm not all this other stuff.
我现在代表着真实存在的变性人群体
I represent the transgender community, and it's a real thing.
最新美剧下载
www.ZiMuZu.tv
我没疯  但我也并不完美
I am not crazy, but I do have flaws.
我很聪明
I'm smart.
乱糟玩意儿
All this other stuff?
我很高兴为你效力  布雷塔
Glad to be of service, Britta.
但我还是穿回尿布吧
I want my diaper back.
就连我这种没电视的人都不想看你的剧情
I don't even own a TV and I wouldn't watch that.
是吗  那你的脑洞是什么
Oh yeah, what's your pitch?
不过就是编个故事  有什么难
Oh, well I, I mean, it's not that complicated is it?
大家好
Hello.
你好
大家好
Hello.
大家好吗
How's everyone?
大家好
Hello.
我提议  我们可以学习科学
I have. We could learn about science
或者历史  毕竟这戏是学校里拍的
or history, it's set in a school, after all.
学而时习之  不亦说乎
Why aren't we learning?
我知道光学习还不够  所以
And I know that's not enough, so.
什么的
And so on.
烂
Boo.
也许比我想象得还要考验功力
It's possible there is more skill to it than I thought.
我赢了赢了赢了
Yes, yes, yes.
确实需要功力积累
There is skill to it.
更重要的一点
More importantly,
就是还得轻松愉快  欢乐有趣
it has to be joyful, effortless, fun.
当一部电视剧想要宣扬说教什么观点
TV defeats it's own purpose when it's pushing an agenda,
或者试图击败其他电视剧
or trying to defeat other TV
或者太过自卑或自满时  就会迷失本来意义
or being proud or ashamed of itself for existing.
电视剧就是要让人开怀
It's TV, it's comfort.
电视剧就好像你的知心老友
It's a friend you've known so well, and for so long
他会常伴在你身边
you just let it be with you
而他也难免会遇到不顺
and it needs to be okay for it to have a bad day
或者手机难使
or phone in a day.
我们也要接受他和勒瓦·伯顿一起驾船出海
And it needs to be okay for it to get on a boat with Levar Burton
永远都不再归来
and never come back.
因为最终  他们都会远去
Because eventually, it all will.
-我没事  -我知道
- I'm fine. - I know.
不只是你说的话
It's not just that.
我犯了个非常典型的错误
It's just such a classic mistake, but...
我被自己开的脑洞剧情深深感动了
I got really attached to my pitch.
我脑子里还在播放背景音乐什么的
I had a sound track in my head and everything.
我同意阿布蒂的话
Well I agree with Abed.
而我有个绝对轻松开怀的脑洞
And I have an effortless pitch.
今年这批祖国的花朵成色如何啊
So, how's this semesters crop of apples looking?
布雷塔的学生还没腐烂
Britta's been out rotting.
我数学课上的亚裔小子不想学习
Asian kid in my math class doesn't want to study
因为他不想变成那种典型的亚洲学霸
because he doesn't want to be a stereotype.
逗死我了
It's pretty funny.
听着像是很不错的副线剧情
Sounds like a strong B story.
而我现在说这些再也不会烦到别人
And I can say that stuff without throwing anyone
因为我是电视剧鉴赏课老师
because I teach TV appreciation.
昌  你可以把那个学生调我班上
Chang, you can send that student to me
我好好调教调教他
and we'll make it more serious.
我是学校的心理辅导员  我可以整季戴眼镜
I'm the school shrink I can wear these glasses every episode.
你带着眼镜真的特性感
You are super hot in them.
-真是  -非常好看
- Yeah. - Very hot.
这样一来我和你们在一起也更合理了
This gives me a more solid reason to interact with you
不用拿傻乎乎的委员会当幌子
than a stupid committee.
外说一句  我是拉拉
By the way I'm a lesbian.
所以我没有和杰夫暧昧过
That's why I haven't hit on Jeff.
我是这样的  我教犯罪学
Here's my deal, I teach Criminology.
不过你们看  这是初版的安妮
But look, it's the original Annie.
但我已经变得成熟火辣
But I'm grown up and I'm hot,
不是那种萝莉式火辣
but not little girl hot.
我很开心  这样大家在一起也很合理
And I'm happy and we're all together and it makes sense.
将来的生活一定很美好
We just might live the good life yet.
-院长好  -杰夫瑞院长
- Hi! Dean! - Dean Jeffrey.
院长  我说过别总到教师休息室来
Dean, I told you not to come into the teachers' lounge,
你应该去上院长培养课去了
you're supposed to be in dean class.
我要是不跟老师们多互动  怎么当院长呢
How can I learn to be dean if I can't hang out with teachers?
我们本来应该塑造他人的思想
We're supposed to be shaping minds,
结果却互相塑造了彼此
but we keep shaping each other.
来抱一个
Bring it in.
这个版本里的你会不会经常调教我
In this version, will you tell me what to do a lot?
而我是不是吃了药了
Am I on meds in it?
我这么平易近人
I'm mellow and relatable.
我喜欢
I like it.
我喜欢在格林德尔教书
I would love to teach at Greendale,
我也怀念穿裙子的日子
and I do miss wearing skirts.
那不如搞个超级宏大的设定
Why don't you shallow a horse pill size contrivance,
这样就会开启不少新剧情线
it would open up new areas and dynamics.
剧集从此长盛不衰
And it's evergreen.
好啊  那就这么定了
Well great that's settled.
我们该怎么实现呢
How do we make it real?
安妮  也许你该去找找师范类课程了
Annie, maybe you should start looking into education classes.
你也是  阿布蒂
You too, Abed.
我也许该跟你们说一声  我要搬去洛杉矶了
Well, I should probably tell you guys that I'm moving to Los Angeles.
什么
What?
我就和真正的电视剧制片人一样
Yeah, like a real TV executive
让你们几个尽情发挥
I was letting you guys work your ass off,
因为否决一个创意不会有任何好处
because there's no profit in saying no to an idea,
不过我也该承认是放手的时候了
but now that it's time for me to commit I have to pass.
我在福克斯台一档节目里当私人助理
I got a job as a PA on a Fox show,
片场是一个电玩游戏演播室
it's in a video game studio.
就好像「我为喜剧狂」加上「IT狂人」
It's like 30 Rock, meets IT Crowd,
再加上我
meets, well me.
-我也在成长  -太好了阿布蒂
- I'm growin' up. - That's so great Abed.
-恭喜你  阿布蒂  -真为你高兴
- Congratulations Abed.  - I'm so happy for you.
但你还会回来的吧
But you're coming back right?
可能
Maybe.
大概
Probably.
也许吧
Maybe.
说好了要六季一影的
That's six seasons and a movie.
杰夫  我知道透过镜头看生活
Jeff I know it comforts you
能让你更安心自在
to look at things through that metal lens,
但这是现实生活
but this is reality.
电视剧的基础可不是常识
TV's rules aren't based on common sense.
而是制作商榨干最后一滴价值的欲望
They're based on the studio wanting to milk their properties dry.
说得好
Here here.
为这话干杯  为阿布蒂干杯
Cheers to that and cheers to Abed.
干杯
Cheers!
怎么了  杰夫瑞
What, Jeffrey?
什么的
And so on.
安妮  我回家了
Annie I'm home.
回来啦
Hey there.
今天怎么样啊
How was your day?
有什么好玩的事吗
Did anything funny happen?
谁在乎呢
Who cares.
你过得怎么样
How was your day?
挺好  塞巴斯蒂安画了画
Good. Sebastian did some drawing.
塞巴斯蒂安
Sebastian?
让我们看看他
Let's look at him.
塞巴斯蒂安
Sebastian.
回你的儿童区去吧
Back to your child area.
我爱你
I love you.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
这真是你想要的吗
Is this really what you want?
当然了
Of course.
家里再养条狗更好
I mean, I'd be fine with a dog too.
但...全看你想要什么
But, whatever you want.
你真的知道我想要什么吗
Do you have any idea what I want?
知道吧
Yes.
你怎么进来的
How'd you get in here?
我把备用钥匙拔了
I pulled the spare key
这样院长就不会把它们藏在门垫下面了
so the dean would stop leaving them under the welcome mat.
你怎么莫名其妙就走了
You left weirdly.
这会儿还能做什么正常的事呢
Well, there's no normal way to do anything now.
是啊
Yeah.
你会过得好好的  知道吗
You're gonna be fine, you know.
我不想好好的
I don't wanna be fine.
我想像25岁的小青年那样出去闯世界
I wanna be 25 and heading out into the world.
我想在沙滩上大睡一觉
I wanna fall asleep on a beach
第二天起来仍然可以大摇大摆
and be able to walk the next day,
或者来了兴致就熬个通宵
or stay up all night on accident.
我想看都不看随便套件T恤
I wanna wear a t-shirt without looking
就好像我已忘记了如何打扮
like I forgot to get dressed.
我想对艾滋病心存惧意
I want to be terrified of AIDS,
我也想对那些东西发表意见  那种
I want to have an opinion about those,
无聊到死的漫威电影
boring ass Marvel movies.
而且我想让我这些意见
And I want those opinions
能引起电影制作者的关注
to be of any concern to the people making them.
我想能在一个地方居住超过一年
Well I want to live in the same home for more than a year,
点酒喝的时候不会心头发憷
order wine without feeling nervous,
简历上只会有各种白痴错误而不是拙劣的谎言
have a resume full of crazy mistakes instead of crazy lies.
我想拥有故事  智慧和正常的三观
I want stories and wisdom, perspective.
我希望自己能一呼百应
I wanna have so much behind me
而不是屈从于眼前的一切
I'm not a slave to what's in front of me,
尤其是那些...
especially these
无趣俗套的漫威电影
flavorless unremarkable Marvel movie.
那些电影有什么大不了的
They are so not a big deal!
-就是的  -不就那么点事儿么
- I know! - It's just all there is!
没错  你就该这么说
Yes, and you get to say that!
如果我这么说就死定了
I could screw myself if I say it,
我压力很大  但你不必压抑啊
but there's pressures on me you don't have to live under,
只要你接受自己年老色衰的事实
if you accept that you're older.
让那些哄小孩的东西一边玩去
And let the kid stuff go.
我会放你走的  安妮
I let you go, Annie.
从我的手中  从我的脑海中
From my hands and my head.
还有我的心中
The heart,
愤青一点说  心灵代表了鸡鸡
which cynics say is code for penis,
心性使然  鸡随所动
wants what it wants.
但我会放你走的
But I let you go.
其他人要来了
The others are coming.
我觉得你应该跟我吻别一下
I think you should kiss me goodbye
不然你的余生都会后悔不已的
or you might regret it for the rest of your life.
那你呢
What about you?
我会后悔一个星期吧  我才二十多岁嘛
Oh, I'll regret the kiss for a week, I'm in my 20s.
谁在乎呢
Who cares?
打扰到你们了吗
Are we interrupting?
别恶心了好不好
Stop being gross!
你们是在拍未经授权的季终戏吗
Are you guys doing an unauthorized finale in here?
不厚道
Not cool.
阿布蒂  我知道透过镜头看生活
Abed, I know it gives you comfort to see everything
能让你安心自在
through that metal lens,
但我们俩只是在跟自习室道别而已
but we were just saying goodbye to the room.
第六季再见
For Season Six.
至于第七季  天晓得
Season Seven, who knows?
我们也管不了的
It's out of our hands.
变数太多
Too many variables.
酷  酷酷
Cool. Cool, cool.
酷酷
Cool, cool.
酷
Cool.
我刚刚是每季说一个酷
That was one cool for each season.
再说一遍
Wait, do it again.
我想试一下
I want to try something.
酷  酷酷
Cool.  Cool, cool.
酷
Cool.
酷酷
Cool, cool.
第四季时我放了个屁
I farted during the fourth one.
内部笑点
It's an inside joke.
我会想你们的
I'm gonna miss you guys.
太基
Gay.
我觉得大家应该这么做
You know what I think everybody should do,
作为一个谦卑的局外人  半路加入成功定位
as a humble outsider that came in and nailed it?
我觉得大家都应该想象一下
I think everyone should imagine
各自对第七季的脑洞版本
their own personal version of Season Seven
不要跟任何人分享
and not share it with anyone.
也许这样真的会变成现实
And then maybe it'll come true.
不许有任何剪辑转场
No cutting to any of them.
如果切镜头  那就不会成真了
If you cut to it, it won't come true.
现在你们不再是学习小组了
You just stopped being a study group.
我现在正式宣布你们是「废柴联盟」
I hereby pronounce you a community.
布丽安娜  你是努力的理想主义者
Brianna, you're the driven idealist.
凯莉  你是热情如火
Kaylee, you're the fiery passionate one.
我们会获得无尽的欢乐
We might have a fun no strings
麦肯齐  古怪死宅妹
and Mackenzie, the kooky nerdy one,
海莉  另外一种怪胎
and Hailey, the other nerdy one!
大家应该成为最好的朋友  一起玩枕头大战
You guys should be best friends and have pillow fights.
菲比  是白富美
And there's Phoebe, the wise one.
不对吗  你也是怪胎
No? You're nerdy too?
好吧  其他人都是红发美女
Okay, and the rest of you are the redhead ones.
我们要一起度过非常疯狂的时光
And we're gonna have some pretty crazy times,
而到最后  你们都会离开  被新人取代
and eventually you'll leave and be replaced by new ones.
现在这种事我已经应付得相当自如了
And that's something I'm equipped to handle now.
我在这方面简直是登峰造极
I'm sort of the hero that way.
我们可以将镜头切到家里的  对吧
We can cut to them at home though, right?
我是说自己动手
I mean by ourselves?
当然
Sure.
我喜欢和你们在一起
I love that I got to be with you guys.
-太基  -你们拯救了我的生活
- Gay. - You saved my life,
永远改变了它
and changed it forever.
基爆啦
Gay!
谢谢
Thank you.
我是基佬
I'm gay.
我真的是基佬
I'm for real gay.
我是真·基佬无疑
I'm legit gay!
BGM: Ends of the Earth by Lord Huron
* Oh, there's a river that winds on forever *
* I'm gonna see where it leads. *
* Oh, there's a mountain that no man has mounted *
* I'm gonna stand on the peak. *
* Out there's a land that time don't command. *
* Wanna be the first to arrive. *
* No time for ponderin' why I'm a-wanderin. *
* Nowhere the buses lay. *
* To the ends, to the ends would you follow me? *
* There's a world that was meant for us to see. *
* To the ends of the earth would you follow me? *
这才是好剧啊
This is the show.
没错  太对了
Right, that's right.
#还有一电影
「废柴联盟」  热门剧集现在化身热门桌游
Community! The hit show is now a hit board game.
更像是我很无聊的游戏吧
More like an I'm bored game.
王牌
闭嘴  伦纳德
Shut up, Leonard.
你就像是德国木偶制作师
You look like a German puppet maker
身上还有教堂里面的味道
and smell like the inside of a church.
讲解游戏规则的广告什么的
Blah, blah, blah commercial video describing the rules of gameplay.
我喜欢你  伦纳德
I like you, Leonard.
作为朋友
As a friend.
抱歉布雷塔  但这段友谊有赚头啊
Sorry Britta, but that friendship just got a benefit.
收集其他玩家的身份信息
Collect all the other players' identities
直接去幻梦空间
成为第一个能识别出
and be the first to figure out
游戏是否是电视剧的一部分  或是
if the game is part of the show or,
我知道了
I got it.
整个剧集都是在这个游戏内发生的
The whole show is happening inside this game.
那解释一下这个
Then explain this.
这是啥
What is it?
这是个剧本
It's a script
写的是第六季结尾的伪广告
of a fake commercial at the end of Season Six,
由咱们家主演
starring this family.
抱歉  老爸
Sorry, dad.
好像我赢了
Guess I win.
你个白痴孩子
You stupid child.
这里根本就没有赢家
Nobody's winning anything.
你没看出来吗
Don't you see?
这意味着我们根本是不存在的
This means we don't exist.
我们不是由上帝创造  而是因笑话而生
We're not created by God, we're created by a joke.
我们从未出生  也不会真正活着
We were never born, and we will never actually live.
游戏不含骰子  部分需要组装
Dice not included. Some assembly required.
各种感知  欲望和现实之间的连线
Lines between perception, desire, and reality
可能会变得模糊  过多或可互换
may become blurred, redundant, or interchangeable.
角色之间可能会互相乱搞
Characters may hook up
完全不在乎你曾经的感情投入
with no regard for your emotional investment.
部分单集太过概念化所以不搞笑
Some episodes too conceptual to be funny.
有些太搞笑以至于有代入感
Some too funny to be immersive,
有些代入感太强  所以还是不搞笑
and some so immersive they still aren't funny.
每季之间的连贯性可能跳跃很大
Consistency between seasons may vary.
收视率将会以一种神秘过时的系统衡量
Viewers may be measured by a secretive obsolete system
选择基准是该观众是否
based on selected participants
在观看中坚持手写观后感
keeping handwritten journals of what they watch.
剧集也许会被取消或移至网络播出
Show may be cancelled and moved to the Internet,
于是发现其实一直以来的观众居然有千万之多
where it turns out tens of millions were watching
也许这并不重要
the whole time, may not matter.
自恋编剧会在伪广告结尾时
Fake commercial may end with disclaimer gag
加入声明般的笑点  其实就是陷入一种
which may descend into vain Chuck Lorre-esque rant
「生活大爆炸」编剧兼制片人
查克·洛尔式的絮絮叨叨
by narcissistic creator.
编剧不固定
Creator may be unstable.
心理治疗师也许会建议编剧
Therapist may have told creator this is not
这样你整个人并不会变好
how you make yourself a good person.
在我们无视或虐待身边事物时生命在不断流失
Life may pass by while we ignore or mistreat those close to us.
而在我们身边的可能就是那些观众
Those close to us may be those watching.
那些人也许想知道我是爱他们的
Those people may want to know I love them
但这话我是说不出口的
but I may be incapable of saying it.
玩具内含儿童食管大小的部件
Contains pieces the size of a child's esophagus.
■
最新美剧下载请登录字幕组网站
www.ZiMuZu.tv
扫描左边二维码关注我们的微信号
或搜索微信号: ustvboom
非常欢迎爱好者加入字幕组一起翻译海外影视剧
■
你看懂了吗
Did you get any of that?